experience-essential-oils.com 2015-05-11

# Privacy Policy for Experience-Essential-Oils.com

This Privacy Policy was developed because **we recognize that your privacy is important.** This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Experience-Essential-Oils.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

Experience-Essential-Oils strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.

### Personal Information

Experience-Essential-Oils collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and signup to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.

### Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser tenable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Experience-Essential-Oils to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our website to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

### Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

### Release of Information

If Experience-Essential-Oils is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in controland practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

### How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.

### Updates and Effective Date

Experience-Essential-Oils reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

### Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to Experience-Essential-Oils Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. Thank you for reviewing Experience-Essential-Oils Privacy Policy.

[Return from **Privacy Policy** to **Experience Essential Oils**](http://www.experience-essential-oils.com/)

_**Ready to Discover All of   YOU in 2015?**_

[ **Find the Gift of You   and Your Inner GPS with Nan's Coaching and Intuitive Guidance **](http://www.experience-essential-oils.com/nan-martin-client-testimonials.html)  

_**  **__**"Nan's   coaching helped me quickly change my self-sabotaging beliefs so I could discover &  follow my dream career!"-Deb C.**_

 _ **  "Nan nails it and gets right to the core root issues every time I work with her.  What a fantastic investment for yourself!"-Diane G.**_

* * *

 _ **Read Nan's Book!  
**_

**Learn howEssential Oils and Coaching can help you _Break Through Emotional Barriers Now_! **

* * *

### **_Sign up for the Free E-zine and Receive  
_**

_a copy of_   
**_"How Therapeutic Essential Oils Help Us Recover our Emotional Wellbeing One Oil at a Time!"_**

* * *

**_It's Here  
Using Essential Oils for People and their Animals Online Training Course!_**

* * *

* * *

[Experience Essential Oils  
on Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/ExperienceEssentialOils "Experience Essential Oils")

* * *

###   
The Oil Shop is Open!

**Searching for**  
 **Therapeutic Grade Essential Oils**  
 **Online?**

Look no further! Place your order at our online essential oil store, The [Oil Shop](http://shop.experience-essential-oils.com/)!

For Canadian and international orders please contact me with a product request and shipping address for a quote today!
